<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Standalone test spies, stubs and mocks for JavaScript. Works with any unit testing framework 2023</title>
	<atom:link href="https://w.sinonjs.org/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://w.sinonjs.org/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:31:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>When will India announce the World Cup schedule?</title>
		<link>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/when-will-india-announce-the-world-cup-schedule/</link>
					<comments>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/when-will-india-announce-the-world-cup-schedule/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCCI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Cup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Cup Cricket]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w.sinonjs.org/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are less than four and a half months left for the start of the World Cup. The host Indian board BCCI has not announced the final schedule yet. Teams usually plan...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There are less than four and a half months left for the start of the World Cup. The host Indian board BCCI has not announced the final schedule yet. Teams usually plan and prepare depending on the World Cup schedule. But the parties are in the dark as they have not received it even in the last week of May.</p>



<p>The BCCI said it will take a few more days to finalize the 2023 World Cup schedule. A special general meeting of the BCCI was held in Ahmedabad on Saturday. After the meeting, BCCI Secretary Jai Shah told the media, &#8216;The venue of the World Cup will be announced at a press conference during the final of the Test Championship. Then the complete schedule of the tournament will be published.</p>



<p>The final of the ICC Test Championship will begin on June 7 at The Oval. India-Australia will face each other.</p>



<p>Chandika Hathurusinghe, the head coach of the Bangladesh team, regretted not getting the World Cup schedule at the end of April. On the last day of the national team&#8217;s camp in Sylhet, whether the World Cup schedule was not announced was a problem, he said, &#8216;It is not only affecting us, it is affecting everyone. It is better if it is announced earlier. A little clearer idea is obtained.&#8217;</p>



<p>The last ODI World Cup was held in England. Organized by the England and Wales Cricket Board (ECB), the tournament began on 31 May 2019. The schedule was released 400 days ago—on April 26, 2018.</p>



<p>Like last time, 10 teams are participating in the World Cup. Meanwhile, Bangladesh, India, Pakistan, Australia, England, South Africa, New Zealand and Afghanistan have confirmed participation. The two teams will be finalized through the qualifiers, which will be held next month, in Zimbabwe. Among the 10 teams shortlisted are two former world champions West Indies and Sri Lanka and two full ICC members Zimbabwe and Ireland.</p>



<p>According to various media reports, the possible start date of the 2023 World Cup is October 5, the final on November 19. England-New Zealand may face each other in the opening match.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/when-will-india-announce-the-world-cup-schedule/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hazlewood in Australia&#8217;s final squad, Indian standby Jaiswal</title>
		<link>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/hazlewood-in-australias-final-squad-indian-standby-jaiswal/</link>
					<comments>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/hazlewood-in-australias-final-squad-indian-standby-jaiswal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia cricket team]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ICC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indian cricket team]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Test Championship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w.sinonjs.org/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Whether Josh Hazlewood, who is waiting to be fit, will be there, was in doubt. Finally, Australia has announced the final team of the World Test Championship with this pacer. India will...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Whether Josh Hazlewood, who is waiting to be fit, will be there, was in doubt. Finally, Australia has announced the final team of the World Test Championship with this pacer. India will be Australia&#8217;s opponent in the final, which will begin on June 7 at the Oval.</p>



<p>Pacer Hazlewood and all-rounder Mitchell Marsh — both withdrew from the IPL early with injuries. There was also talk that Hazlewood would be replaced by Michael Nesser. Hazlewood is finally in the main team. Cricket Australia gave the final 15-man squad to the ICC on Sunday. Marsh has been kept as standby. Matthew Renshaw also went to the standby list with Marsh from the 17-man squad.</p>



<p>Nesser and Shane Abbott will assist the Australian team in training. Wicketkeeper Josh Inglis has been kept as backup to Alex Carey in the main team. Todd Murphy is the spinner along with Nathan Lyon.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, India did not make any changes in the original team of 15 people. However, Yasaswi Jaiswal has been brought in place of Ruturaj Gaikwad who is on standby. It is known that Gaikwad has removed himself because he will get married.</p>



<p>Jaiswal has had a great season for Rajasthan Royals in the IPL. He scored 625 runs in 14 matches at a strike rate of 163.61. Suryakumar Yadav and Mukesh Kumar are on standby with Jaiswal.</p>



<p>Those whose teams were earlier eliminated from the IPL have already gone to England to start training. Virat Kohli is also in this team.</p>



<p>This is going to be the second final of the World Test Championship. India lost to New Zealand in the final of the last season.</p>



<p>Team Australia:<br>Pat Cummins (captain), Scott Boland, Alex Carey (wicketkeeper), Cameron Greene, Marcus Harris, Josh Hazlewood, Travis Head, Josh Inglis (wicketkeeper), Usman Khawaja, Marnus Labuschagne, Nathan Lyon, Todd Murphy, Steve Smith (Vice-Captain), Mitchell Starc, David Warner.</p>



<p>Standby: Mitchell Marsh, Matthew Renshaw.</p>



<p>Team India:<br>Rohit Sharma (captain), Shubman Gill, Cheteshwar Pujara, Virat Kohli, Ajinkya Rahane, Srikar Bharat (wicketkeeper), Ravichandran Ashwin, Ravindra Jadeja, Akshar Patel, Shardul Thakur, Mohammad Shami, Mohammad Siraj, Umesh Yadav, Jaydev Unadkat , Ishan Kishan (wicketkeeper).</p>



<p>Standby: Yasswi Jaiswal, Mukesh Kumar, Suryakumar Yadav.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/hazlewood-in-australias-final-squad-indian-standby-jaiswal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Erdogan elected president of Turkey for the third term</title>
		<link>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/erdogan-elected-president-of-turkey-for-the-third-term/</link>
					<comments>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/erdogan-elected-president-of-turkey-for-the-third-term/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[middle east]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Recep Tayyip Erdogan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Türkiye]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w.sinonjs.org/?p=11</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Recep Tayyip Erdogan has been elected for the third consecutive term as the President of Turkey. He won the second round of the presidential election held in the country on Sunday. Turkey&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Recep Tayyip Erdogan has been elected for the third consecutive term as the President of Turkey. He won the second round of the presidential election held in the country on Sunday.</p>



<p>Turkey&#8217;s state news agency Anadolu reported that 97 percent of the votes had been counted. Erdoğan got 52.1 percent of the votes. And the candidate of the main opposition alliance, Kemal Kilicdarolu, got 47.9 percent of the votes. Erdoğan was re-elected as the private president.</p>



<p>National elections were held in Turkey on May 14. At that time, no presidential candidate received 50 percent of the vote. Erdogan came closest to winning with 49.5 percent of the vote. Next was Kemal Kilicdarolu. His vote was 44.8 percent. As a result, the vote was conducted in the second round.</p>



<p>Erdogan has been serving as the president of Turkey since 2014. Before that, he was the country&#8217;s prime minister from 2003 to 2014. And he was the mayor of Istanbul from 1994 to 1998.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/erdogan-elected-president-of-turkey-for-the-third-term/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Tetreamra]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w.sinonjs.org/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://w.sinonjs.org/2023/05/28/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
